...two, three, four,
fve, six, seven,
eight, nine and ten.
Cat!
Julio. No, Julio!
Julio, no! Dirty. Come.
INTER BARRlO TOURNAMENT
SEMl-FlNAL LA CENlZA 0 - LA VEGA 1
16 YEARS LATER
Go up, Cat! Up!
Foul!
Give him a red card!
Stop it! Stop it!
When you're trapped, look for help.
Relax, that dude is
just a fatty like you.
Eight minutes!
Come on boys, you can do it.
Oh my God!
Defense!
Pray this match
turns around, motherfucker.
We're going to mob you.
Chill, bro!
If you get red carded we're screwed.
Stay put. Stay put.
Come on, Max.
Cat...
Like in the neighborhood.
Five minutes.
Fly, Cat! Go!
Go for it!
Do it! Do it!
Goal!
Yes!
One more!
One more and we're in the final!
That's it.
Go up and stay there.
Wait for the pass.
He got it back!
Go Dani, go Dani.
Goal!
Next time you disobey me
I'm gonna kick your ass!
You're a freak!
Congratulations!
What a goal, son!
Julio!
Mom!
Congratulations.
Did you see my boys?
-Now you're in the finals, right?
-Yes, our next match.
What a goalie!
Where are they?
Bravo! Ceniza, Bravo!
You're too much!
One more win and you'll leave
your boyfriend for me?
-You think you're that good?
-What game were you watching?
The baseball game on the other field.
Great game.
-So you like baseball.
-It's a pity you don't play baseball.
-You could make some real money.
-Shut up.
Let's go before they close
the liquor store.
Daniel!
I've been busting my balls all season
to get this man to come to a game.
He chose the best day.
This is Edgar Quintana.
He's a talent scout
for the Caracas Football Club.
Julio and Daniel.
What a game, what a game.
We're having a tryout
this week for our club.
We're looking for our next generation.
Hold on,
I'm not telling you that you will
play for the Caracas Football Club,
I'm just inviting you to the tryouts.
How old are you?
-Seventeen... in a few months.
-Next year.
Well, you'll be the youngest of thirty
contenders dying to get drafted.
Hold on, hold on.
He's little and fast.
But if he gets hurt it'll fuck up
our chances for the final.
What do you want to do?
I want to play
for Venezuela with Julio.
But if it's between me and him,
I'll have to kick his fat ass.
You never know, kid.
The way you two play together,
you may live your dream.
I'm going to buy a Caracas bandana.
-Wait till we get in, Ma.
-Of course you will.
Of course.
-Smells good. What is it?
-Beef.
It's not done yet.
Yum. This is fucking glorious.
Do you have to talk
like a monkey in front of Ma?
-Ma. Let's send him back.
-No.
What time's the party?
Right now, we gotta go help Max
set up the whole thing.
I'll come later
with the beef and beans.
-Have you seen the bottle opener?
-Drawer.
Cat, go get the empty beer
crates out back.
What? You don't have hands?
-Just a favor.
-Go sweetie, get the crate, come on.
Julio.
Sugar has gone up again.
I've got four cakes to bake tomorrow
and I've run out.
Is that enough?
-I'll pay you back tomorrow.
-Don't worry, Ma.
Open up, dickhead.
Don't talk like that in front of Ma,
fag!
-Julio.
-Open up!
What's up, Cat? Where's your key?
How long are you gonna take, dude?
Maximiliano.
How's the super goalkeeper
from La Ceniza?
Great game!
-You're a super goalkeeper?
-Of course.
-Can you stop these balls?
-Hey!
There's a bunch of hoodlums coming
home and we need to make room.
Come on, lets go.
God bless. Take care. See you there
later. Don't drink too much!
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
We're gonna be champions!
-Where you going, Cat?
-I was looking for you. I'm bored.
Bored?
Look around you, you little fag!
These people are here because of you.
How many goals have you scored
this season?
-I don't know.
-Bullshit! How many? Including today.
-lncluding today?
-Of course.
Seven more than you.
Eighteen? Good!
-We're gonna have eighteen shots!
-I've got school tomorrow, brother.
He's got school, the pretty girl.
Faggot.
-Control your crazy friend.
-Show some respect.
Petare is tough.
We're tougher than them.
-Have you danced yet?
-My leg's fucked up.
-My leg's sore from the game.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Women say that a guy who can dance,
can fuck.
So if they don't see you dancing,
they'll know you don't fuck.
And if you don't fuck,
you're fucked.
Listen to me. I fuck.
-You fuck?
-I fuck.
You? You fuck.
Your hand's not a girl!
Let's go have something
to eat with Ma, bro.
-Go dance with Mom.
-I'm gonna dance with your girlfriend.
What's up, Morocho?
Where are you going?
-Home.
-No you're not. I want to dance.
So you wanna dance?
Where's your boyfriend?
Doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter?
No, I don't want trouble.
I want to dance.
Hey Cat, I'm taking Caro home.
You want a ride?
Bye, Caro.
No, thanks. I already drank too much.
They'll be superstars like you.
-I wasn't a superstar.
-Of course you were.
Julio will be out of 'the life'.
They're not in yet.
It's a tryout. A lot of kids.
They'll get in. I know it.
Shit.
Stay, my love.
I'll make breakfast for all of us.
It doesn't matter.
That'd be perfect.
But I can't.
I have to go.
When you decide to tell her the truth,
you'll have a family here.
-I love you.
-I love you, too.
-Good morning, Cat.
-Hi, Ma.
-One arepa?
-No, two.
-She pissed me off last night.
-Why?
She was claiming I left her alone.
-Hey, what's up? All good?
-One bag.
What's up, dude?
-You suck.
-You can't even do three.
-I'll give you ten.
-Ten? Okay, you count.
Four, five, six... eight,
-nine.
-You lost.
Coward.
-Coward?
-You're a coward.
Stop it.
-What's up, Zamuro?
-What the hell is going on? Get out!
Shut the fuck up, old man!
-The money.
-I paid, I already paid.
-Lie to me again!
-I paid Morocho.
What are you saying? Stop lying.
Be cool.
Tell me another lie.
Are you an asshole?
Did you pay or not?
You've got two days.
Otherwise this guy will
hunt you down and kill you.
Now you know, you cocksucker.
We'll be running up and down
the field the entire game.
Total Football.
No pussies, no dives.
Are you listening, Yobert?
Whatever you say, Coach.
But!
Before we begin our most
important week of training.
Daniel and Julio, make a wall!
Come on! Move it!
The sun's burning, bro, so move it.
We all know
that their good luck
is thanks to us. So...
Congratulations, boys!
Come on. Make them pay!
Get all that shit out!
Don't be a coward, Daniel!
Goal, dude!
-That was a foul.
-Talk to the ref.
Yeah, right. ""Talk to the ref"".
-Two-one. Learn to play defense.
-I score goals, dumbass.
No.
You wait for the ball to come to you.
The real game is fought in the back.
I've never seen a game
won without any goals scored.
I've never seen you beat me here.
Watch me.
Hold on. What happened there?
Oh man.
Here it is.
Don't worry, dude.
Careful, dude, I can beat you.
How'd it go with Sol last night?
-She seemed really into you.
-You think? She has a boyfriend.
Nah, man. Really.
The way she looked at you.
She was ready to play the trombone.
You don't know the trombone?
Oh man! You gotta aim for that
when you pop your cherry.
I was getting this great blow job.
What was his name?
Listen, Cat. This is good advice.
So she kept going down, down.
Oh baby! To suck on my balls!
It's great getting your balls sucked.
Then she told me to get on my knees.
-And she started to lick my...
-You made a girl lick your ass!?
I didn't make her do anything.
Then she started with her hand.
No, man. What the hell is that?
-Three! Game over.
-You're not serious.
No, bye-bye. You're out.
Did you do that at home?
On your bed, man.
Ready, boss?
Okay, we're on our way.
Came on, Cat. Let's go.
-Where?
-Come on.
-Do you have the tickets?
-The tickets? One ticket.
Come on.
Get in, get in. Hurry.
Hold on. Hold on.
You deal better than this guy.
That's why I put you in
charge of collecting.
But we don't hurt the family.
If you touch him again,
we've all got trouble.
Clear?
Let's go watch some football.
Go red, go red, go red.
Are you crazy?
I could've had a gun or something.
Yeah, right.
-Why didn't you go to school today?
-ls your mom home?
I don't know. You want some lunch?
Can you keep a secret?
Have you tried my mom's 'tres leches'?
Everyone has tried your mom's cakes.
They're the best.
Do you know what the trombone is?
I'm pregnant.
-No. Is it mine?
-How could it be yours?
Have you told your family?
They'll kill me.
I'm going to get rid of it.
Get rid of it?
Will you come with me?
You're the only one who knows.
Come on. Let's train for the final.
Just a few laps.
Petare!
The largest barrio in the country!
Tournament champions
three years running!
Twelve more goals than us this year!
And the best defense in the league!
Known for breaking attackers' legs!
Daniel Flores! Go again!
Use your wooden leg!
It won't get easier from here!
The Caracas coach
is ten times tougher than me.
You've gotta be at your best.
So, eat your mom's cooking,
and go to bed early.
No smoking. No drinking.
And no sex.
That's an easy one
for the Virgin Mary here.
Oh man, you wont be able to play...
Good one.
Relax, Coach. We'll be clean.
-Bye.
-I hope so.
Bye, Coach.
Julio is a big guy.
He casts a big shadow.
But you need to step out from it.
The day you do, you'll fly.
Did you see the game last night?
He hit a homerun like this.
And ran like this.
The superstar.
How's it going?
Fine, fine.
What's up, superstar?
Show us a trick.
-I gotta get home.
-Come on. Show us.
-I don't have a ball.
-I know you don't have balls.
Use this. Quickly.
Okay. One, two, three.
I lost it.
-How much did you pay for these cleats?
-Hey.
Give me your football shoes.
Give them to me,
you know I'm crazy.
Grab them.
Go away. Get the fuck out of here.
-You don't know what ""go away"" means?
-Get out of here.
No way, dude. They're too big.
They smell like dog shit.
Let's go, let's go.
What is it?
Hi Cat, what happened?
Son, what is it?
What's that for?
-Did something happen?
-No.
What do you mean ""no""?
What are you looking for?
-Cat, tell me what happened.
-Nothing happened.
What do you mean ""nothing""?
-Be careful, where you going?
-Doesn't matter.
-Chicken.
-You can't reach.
You're too short.
You're already growing tits.
They were too big. If they were small,
I would've kept them.
The dude looked like an idiot
trying to reach them.
What's happening, little shits?
Go get those shoes down.
Go get them.
Go get the shoes down.
Fuck!
Ma. Ma.
Help.
Roberto.
Hold on, Ma. Hold on.
-Brother! Are you fucking crazy?
-Please help. She's my mom.
Put her in.
What happened, brother?
I'm coming.
My real girlfriend was there.
And this other chick was gesturing
over to me, really obvious.
What did she say?
No wait.
The chick went to the bathroom.
-Hurry up please.
-Calm down, brother. Hold on.
With my girlfriend right next to me.
-She's bleeding too much.
-We're almost there. Talk to her.
This piece of shit doesn't work.
And the chick was staring at me
for like an hour.
Don't look there, Camilo. Look ahead.
The cell phone.
Sir, can I borrow your cell phone?
Hello.
Julio, brother. We're on our way to
the hospital. I don't know what to do.
What happened, Cat?
Where you going, dude?
What happened, Daniel?
I found her.
Where?
-On the stairway.
-Where?
-Near Antonio's.
-You didn't see anything?
-No.
-How did you find out?
-Who else was there?
-Fuck, man. Are you a cop or what?
Am I a cop? Fuck off.
You want to know who
killed her, don't you?
So don't fuck with me
with your cop bullshit.
Who shot her?
I don't know.
So you didn't see anything?
Who else was there?
The glue sniffers.
Let's go.
You don't have to come.
What?
To the clinic.
I'll go myself.
I'll come with you.
My mom saved my life.
But I couldn't save hers.
Condolences, brother.
I'm sorry, Cat.
From Morocho and the brothers.
Bury her properly.
-No thanks.
-What is it?
I don't want to do that.
What don't you want to do?
Bury Mom with dirty money.
What I bring home is sacred.
This is from my brothers.
Get the fuck out of my face.
Go!
Sorry, dude.
There, there. Here it comes.
Rincon shoots!
What a great save. What a shot!
The tryout's tomorrow.
No. Her burial is tomorrow.
The tryout's in the afternoon.
You can make it.
What are you going to do?
My duty.
Julio, I want to go.
Then go.
I need you there, brother.
Together we have a better chance.
I'm going to see Morocho.
What for?
Shit, Coach.
Don't tell me you're as stupid as he is.
Don't you know Morocho
controls everything here?
Morocho must know
what the fuck happened.
I still haven't told Edgar
about your mom.
No. Don't tell him.
I don't want those people's pity.
Long, long, long.
I'm gonna go.
Goal!
Go watch your game.
Let's go, Julio.
Ma would be glad to see us there.
Together.
Sir, these are the two prospects
I told you about. Julio and Daniel.
Hello.
You're late.
Go play a softball game.
There's no set time for those.
We're here to compete.
-The bathrooms?
-Locked.
One side to the other.
Keep the ball close to you.
In and out.
Don't lose the ball.
You're tired.
Save it for the game.
Let's show these guys
how we play in La Ceniza.
Too skinny.
Left side, grab a blue vest.
Right side, green vest.
Come on people, move those legs.
We're not on vacation.
Hey, hey. You two.
Yes, you two. Separate teams.
He's my brother. He's my brother.
I'm your tryout, Cat.
If you can beat me,
you can beat anyone.
Here, here.
Modern football does not exist
without attacking wingmen!
You two! Go check your make-up!
This is not a girl's sport.
You gotta leave
your balls on the field.
You, lady. Out.
The forward. Yes, you.
How many one-on-ones
you think you can miss in one game?
Fresh legs. Come on. Quick.
Julio.
I can't be chasing the ball
like an idiot.
Julio, what is it?
Who killed her?
Who killed her, Daniel?
What's wrong, Julio?
Game over, worms.
If any of you managed to fool us into
thinking you can play football,
we'll call you.
Thank you, Sir.
Do we have his info?
Of course.
Cool, isn't it? Here, for your kid.
This is great.
Shit, lker.
Dude, Petare will want to kidnap us,
thinking we're rich kids.
How did it go at Caracas FC?
What do you know?
Who was it, man?
I know how you feel.
Come. Let's get a drink.
So, you don't know?
Motherfucker.
Aren't you the boss here?
This is your town.
People come to you.
They want medicine, to fix their place,
new uniforms.
My mother is dead.
I'm one of yours, your family.
I'm here, man.
Yeah, brother.
You're my family. I know.
So shut up and listen.
Most of these guys
are gonna be dead in two years.
You've got a chance
to get out of the life.
What the fuck?
Are you firing me?
No. I'm saving you.
Saving me from who? From who?
Which one of these
motherfuckers did it?
-Brother.
-Go home.
-Brother, let's go.
-You go.
Think of your brother.
God forbid he gets hurt.
Easy.
Bring him.
Julio!
Come here.
Coach!
-Put his hand here.
-Let me go!
Julio!
Morocho, don't!
Let him go!
No, don't!
Julio!
The pain in your hand will go away.
The pain in your heart won't.
Not if you kill one motherfucker
or a thousand. It's all the same.
You think you're the only one
who's lost someone you loved?
My brother was killed
right in front of my eyes.
Get out of the life, man.
Let him go.
Get his hand fixed.
We need him healthy for the final.
What's the best goal
you've ever seen?
Every time you score.
You're my hero.
Go to sleep.
Do you remember the day I was born?
I know the story but I don't remember.
We were going to a birthday party.
I'd been asking Mom
for a pet for a long time.
And when I heard you
I thought you were a cat.
You and Mom saved me.
Don't leave me alone, brother.
I'll be fine.
Go to sleep.
Do you know how they do it?
Let's go.
I'll look after you.
Are you crazy?
My family will kill me.
My mom saved my life.
You are just like her. Please.
I can't have a baby alone.
-Ready?
-No.
Are you responsible for this?
-Yes.
-No.
-What's the deal here?
-We're leaving.
We're leaving.
-Hello, Caro.
-For you.
-Hey.
-Hi, Coach.
What a coincidence!
I was on my way to your place.
I want to talk to you.
We'll talk on the way. The CFC called.
We've got a meeting.
-When?
-Now.
-Caro, I'm going out with Daniel.
-Bye, Caro.
So I'd been in Colombia
for almost a year.
I had no money left.
I was about to come home.
Then the phone rang
and they told me I made the team.
Fuck kid,
that was the best day of my life.
Coach.
Coach, I was there.
I saw everything.
I saw when my mom got killed.
It was Max.
It was Max, the motherfucker.
And, yes, it was an accident.
And I didn't tell Julio.
But it was my fault.
It was my fault.
Because I'm a coward,
a fucking coward.
You are not a coward.
Coach, Julio could've gotten
killed yesterday.
Your brother is your brother.
Nobody can change that.
Don't tell him.
Forget about it.
The most important thing
for you right now
is this meeting we're going to.
Shit, Daniel, this is not Brazil.
You are unique, Daniel.
You have a talent that
the whole world deserves to see.
And your mom...
She knew that.
And Caracas is the first step.
Don't waste it.
What about Julio?
You can help him better
when you save yourself.
Okay?
Okay.
Did you tell them about my mom?
Do you think you can play
professional football?
What do you think
you need to work on?
His left.
You can't speak?
My defense.
You're skinnier than
my six-year-old daughter.
You need to bulk up.
Build muscle.
You're a good prospect, Daniel.
But if you join the team
you'll need something special.
What's that?
Commitment?
You're not as dumb as you look.
Pay attention.
No partying, no smoking, and
no girlfriends.
This is a good first contract.
You won't have to work.
But once you sign,
your life will be ours.
What about school?
He's still in high school.
We'll let him finish school.
One day he might have to
read his own contracts.
What about my brother?
He's better than me.
Who, the brawler? The one
who walked out during the tryout?
Come to the game on Sunday.
It's the final,
you can watch us play.
My brother is the captain of our team
and the best player in the league.
That way you can put two names
on the contract instead of one.
What you're saying
is that you want two contracts?
-Yes.
-Two contracts or none?
No.
You've got some guts.
I was wrong.
You are much,
much dumber than I imagined.
No, Daniel. Think it through.
Sign that contract.
Very well. Double or nothing then.
You and your brother will have
to play really well on Sunday.
Because if I go to see you,
and you don't win...
You won't see this again.
We're unbeatable together.
See you Sunday.
-Thank you.
-What's happening?
-Justice.
Nelson Guerra is coming to the final.
If we win, we get to play for Caracas.
-I don't play football.
-Where are you going?
I know who killed her.
Where are you going, cocksucker?
Where are you going?
Tell him you killed her,
motherfucker.
Tell him you killed her
and I won't let him kill you.
I already paid.
I haven't killed anyone.
-Talk, you bastard.
-Do it, brother.
He's lying to your face, man.
-He killed your mom.
-I haven't killed anyone.
Tell him, cocksucker.
Tell him you killed her.
Tell and I won't let him kill you.
-Tell him.
-Speak!
This motherfucker
murdered her like trash.
-Brother, don't be a murderer.
-Get out!
No Julio! Don't be a murderer!
-You know it wasn't him.
-Get out of the fucking way!
You're not a killer,
you're my brother.
-I don't care, get out of the way!
-You know it wasn't him!
You little fuck! You took it from me.
-You've fucked everything up.
-You fucked it up.
I gave your brother what he needed:
his revenge.
You think I'm talking about this mess?
I saw you. I saw you in the alley
when you killed her.
When you killed her.
I didn't see your mom show up.
I swear. I was helping you
because you shit your pants.
Get away from us.
Or I'll kill you myself.
I swear I'll kill you.
Go ahead.
You won't be able to cover this one.
Do it!
I loved her too, man.
If you loved her so much,
leave us alone.
I don't want my brother
to know either, but leave us alone.
Stay away.
Are you going through all this shit
just to make a football team?
First to three.
Two-one.
If I win, you have to play in the final.
-Ma doesn't want a murderer for a son.
-You don't give a fuck about Ma.
Stupid! Idiot! Asshole!
Ma saved my life.
I owe her everything.
She wants you alive.
She deserves justice.
You're gonna die!
That's not justice! That's stupidity!
Fuck off, you little shit.
Play the fucking game!
This is the first time in my life
that I have a chance to beat you.
If I win,
you get the fuck out of the house.
You know what, Julio?
When we play together, it's
the best time of my life, brother.
Goal!
The smell of her cakes is fading,
brother.
-You wanna shower first?
-No, you go ahead.
Cat.
Come.
To Mama.
You'll get used to it
by the time we finish the bottle.
You were a gift.
You wanna dance?
Or is your leg still fucked up?
I'm in.
Go for it.
You are a freak, man.
Take it, bro!
What a goal!
Save me a seat next
to you on the bus.
Hey.
See you.
What's that?
-Are you coming to the game?
-No.
I called my mom
and told her everything.
-I'm going back to Barinas today.
-Today?
-And the baby?
-I'm going to have it.
Then see what happens.
I'll visit you. You and the baby.
I hate you.
I love you.
I wish you were the father.
How's the hand?
Ready to crack skulls.
Go on then.
Destroy those fuckers
and bring that trophy to the barrio.
Guys.
Whatever happens today,
to me, you are already champions.
You achieved something
beautiful for our barrio.
Hope.
So when things get ugly out there,
remember that you have each other.
-Let's win.
-Come on!
Let's go.
Over here.
Fuck!
Guys, come here.
Come on, let's go, come here.
Life will always score goals
against us.
That's why every single day
we need to get up
convinced that the game
is still zero-zero.
Otherwise we're fucked, right?
Zero-zero, guys.
Zero-zero.
Look around you. Look at each other.
You are family.
Brothers.
Zero-zero.
In the next forty-five minutes,
you will give everything
for your family.
Julio.
Come on! Yeah.
Something's changed.
-Come back, come back.
-Here, here.
Goal!
Let's put pressure on number 10.
Not number 18, number 10. Okay?
Come on, Ceniza!
Don't turn your back to the ball.
Get in there.
Come on, cover that man.
-What is that?
-Dangerous play, sir.
What the fuck are you ruling?
A penalty kick?
Come on, bro.
It's not over yet. We still need you.
Coach! Coach!
Calm down, take it easy.
-He just threw up.
-Can you get up?
You're fucked, dude.
-Stop that penalty kick.
-Yeah?
What if I don't?
Are you gonna stop it.
That's what I thought.
""Superstar"".
Sub me out, Coach. You need fresh legs.
No way man. We need our captain.
Now you're in charge.
Fix him, Coach. Two contracts or none.
Fix him.
That was shit.
Daniel is right. I can't replace you.
You have to get drafted.
Look at him. Look at him.
You have no idea what that kid
has done to get you here.
What's he done?
We all have secrets, Julio.
Daniel kept his because he loves you.
-Do you love me, brother?
-You're my brother.
Am l?
Come on, we still have time,
let's win this.
We've still got time.
Let's do this. Come on.
Goal! That's it!
You knew.
You knew and you didn't tell me.
I did it for us.
You killed me, man.
You wanted your dream?
There it is, you've got it.
-But you lost a brother.
-Julio, brother.
-Julio.
-We should've left you in the trash.
There's still time.
They killed him!
Leave him!